#### **About Me**

Confident and motivated with Professional experience in interior space planning and architectural elements. Passionate about making the interior and the environment of any space look aesthetically more pleasing for the people using that space. Ability to manage and bring the best in terms of creativity, initiative and efforts and enable to contribute efficiently towards achievement of excellence in work area. Can transfer client ideas into beautiful and functional design solutions.

#### **Skills**

Detail Oriented
Time Management
Good in Communication
AutoCAD
MSOffice
Coral Draw
Photoshop
3DMax

#### **Education**

Diploma in Interior Designing and Decoration, 2010 – 2012 M.S.B.T.E

T.Y.B.Com 2010 Maharashtra State Board

H.S.C 2007 Maharashtra State Board

S.S.C 2005 Maharashtra State Board

# **BHAVIK TANK**

Address Triveni Niwas, Liberty Garden, Road No 03, Malad West, Mumbai 400064 Email tank.bhavik03@gmail.com
Contact +91 9892241452

### **Experience**

## Triiveta, Furniture Showroom 2019 – Current

- Design development and finalizing drawings and specifications.
- Research and design on materials and product sourcing.
- Handle all types of queries from customers related and coordinating with internal team.

# Riso, Restaurant at Vashi Residence at Borivali Z.A.Designs 2016 - 2019

- Work with clients to define project requirements and develop design.
- Conceptualizing and designing all aspects of Interior design projects including design presentations either individually or as part of a team.

# Studio Apartment at Juhu, Mumbai SMAAASH Outlet at Mumbai, Delhi, Noida, Bangalore, Hyderabad, The Orange Lane, 2015-2016

- Create and present interior design concepts in response to client needs.
- Meeting and communicating with clients for project development and progress.
- Supervise work progress, communicate with design team and handle office documentation.

# HUE, Multidesigner Store, Hughes Road, Mumbai Nittrro bespoke Fitness Centre at Breach Candy, Mumbai ARCH AID, 2013 - 2015

- Site measurements, Space planning and preparing detail drawings.
- Assemble materials and finish sample boards.
- Preparing Estimates and BOQ.
- Site supervision, coordinating with contractors, suppliers and venders.
- Research and follow new trends in industry.

#### Language

English Hindi Guiarati Marathi